Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 4: Clothing, 1878-2010; 52 boxes
  - Gray T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    with black P on front
  - Handkerchief, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Orange and white. "78"
    Class of 1878
    Given by Mrs. Graham Hunter, daughter of John Henry Kerr, class of 1878. Used at class reunions.
  - Handkerchief, 1947; 1 box (Box B.9)
    AR.1996.110
    Orange paint on it from raid at Rutgers before 1947 or 1948 football game.
  - Handkerchief, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Black and orange. Silk.
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box B.5)
    Hard safari hat. White. "17"
    Class of 1917
  - Hat, 1939; 1 box (Box B.12)
    Orange cap. "38" 1st reunions.
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box B.12)
    White with orange band. "1926"
    Class of 1926
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box B.12)
    Steel gray and orange, "1922" on front.
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box B.12)
    Black with "V" pin attached.
  - Hat, circa 1896; 1 box (Box B.12)
    Black with orange braid and "PC 94". Pin attached "1746-Sesquicentennial Celebration-1896."
    Class of 1894
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box B.14)
    AR.1998.019
    White with orange and black band.
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box 15)
    Orange and black hat with black brim.
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box 18)
    Navy blue hat with gold lettering "USS Princeton CG 59."
  - Hat, 2010; 1 box (Box 38)
    AR.2010.132
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. White baseball hat.
    Class of 1985
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box 40)
    Black cap with orange "P" and small brim.
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box 45)
    AR.2009.004
    Orange baseball cap with silver logo. "Peter B. Lewis Library Princeton University."
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box 45)
    Gray hat with "1942" logo.
    Class of 1942
  - Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box 45)
    Off-white hat with orange, black and white band.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '74 and U seal. White.
    Class of 1874
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '76. Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '78. Orange with black stripes.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '78. Black with orange stripes.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '79. Blue numbers. White.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '81. Black and orange striped.
    Class of 1881
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '86. Black and orange striped.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '86. Black with three stripes.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '86. Orange with black stripe.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '86 with U seal. White.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '87's. Black.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '87. Black and orange striped.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '87. Black with thin orange stripe.
    George Packer Berry '21
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '88. Single eight's.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '88. Entwining eight's.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '89. Orange.
    Class of 1889
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '89. Black with three stripes.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '90. Black with two stripes.
    Class of 1890
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '90. Black with orange stripes.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '91. Black with orange stripes.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '92. Tigers on black.
    Class of 1892
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '92. Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '94. Black.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '95. Black.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '95. Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    "1895". Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    "1897" with seal. White.
    Class of 1897
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '99. Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    1901. Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    1901. Orange with black border.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    1901. Black.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '01. Black.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '03. Black with stripe.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '03. Black with tigers.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.2)
    '03. White with seal.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    '04. Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1904 Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1904 Black.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1905 Orange.
    Class of 1905
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1907 Orange. Pointed lettering.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1907. Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1907 L. Red and blue.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1907. Black and orange striped.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1907. Black with two stripes.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    "07 L. Blue with red stripe.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1907. Tent with camels.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1908. Orange. Pointed lettering.
    Class of 1908
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1908. Green.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1908. Orange with stripes.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    '08. White with orange and black stripes.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    '09. Orange with tiger.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1909. Black and orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.3)
    1910. Black with orange stripe.
    Class of 1910
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1910. Black with orange stripes.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1910. Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1912.
    Class of 1912
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1913. Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1915.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1918.
    Class of 1918
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1921. Orange.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1921. Orange with black stripe.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1930.
    Class of 1930
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1932.
    Class of 1932
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    1939.
    Class of 1939
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    Eating club bands?
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    Black with 1913 stitched in orange.
  - Hatband, 1909; 1 box (Box B.3)
    AR.1996.041
    White, 1909.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    AR.2000.077
    1942. Orange and black felt.
  - Hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    '76. Orange satin.
  - Hat band, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    with 98 and a tiger head.
  - Hat band, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    with 98 and Princeton shields.
  - Hatband?, Undated; 1 box (Box B.10)
    Orange with black 22.
  - Jacket, Undated; 1 box (Box B.8)
    Jacket patterned. Battle of Princeton 22.
  - Jacket and pants set, Undated; 1 box (Box B.13)
    "1946" on jacket. Orange and white striped corduroy.
    Class of 1946
  - Kilt, sporeen, cap, fake white cloth boot tops., Undated; 1 box (Box B.13)
    Orange and black buffalo plaid.
    Given by Frank Buchner '34.
  - Necktie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    "22 " Black.
  - Necktie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    "22" Orange plaid.
  - Orange Jacket, Undated; 1 box (Box B.8)
    "16" on pocket.
  - Orange tie, 1933; 1 box (Box B.20)
    AR.2001.056
    Orange tie with black "217-8". Commemorates 1933 football season. Princeton scored 217 points.
  - Orange T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    with black triangular Princeton shield on front.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black and pentagonal, outlined on a seal, with "92" in orange.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Orange and round, with "94," a circle around it in black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black and square, with "'94" in orange.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black and pentagonal, outlined on a seal, with "96" in orange.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Orange seal, with "98" in black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Orange and black rendition of a tiger; "'01" on the tiger's side.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Orange and rectangular, "'04" in black; white elastic band.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    White and inverse-T-shaped; "P 1906" in orange and black.
    Class of 1906
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    White seal outlined in orange and black; "P," "07" embroidered in black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    White seal outlined in orange and black; "1909" in black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black and square; "'09," a tiger in orange.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Princeton seal in orange and black, "1910" in orange.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Orange and round, with a black circle, "12" in black inside.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black and round, with orange outline, "1915" in orange.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black with Princeton seal and motto in orange and white, "1916" in white.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black seal with a tiger in orange and white, "22" in countershaded on orange.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black with Princeton seal and motto in orange and white, "1923" in white.
    Class of 1923
  - Patch, 1963; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Orange and round, a tiger on a camel, with a beer mug; "to our Fortieth" in black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Orange and round with black rim; "1926" in black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black and irregularly shaped; tiger with "1926" on the chest and with a "P" beer mug embroidered in orange and white.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    White and round with orange rims; a head of tiger, "Princeton," "1926" in orange and black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Princeton seal and motto, with "1926" embroidered in orange.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black seal, with "27" in orange.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    White seal with a tiger, "1948" embroidered in orange and black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black. "60" in orange.
    Class of 1960
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black and round with orange rim; "1967" in black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    White and rectangular, with two fencing swords crossed in orange, "P," "U," "F," "T" in black.
  - Patch, 1956; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black and square, Princeton seal, "Princeton on the Ohio April 5-7-56" in orange/brown and white.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black badge with a head of tiger, "Tiger Inn" in green, gray and white.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Princeton seal and motto, with drawing of Cleveland Tower in black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Orange and rectangular, with round corners; "Princeton University" in black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    White and round, with a head of tiger in orange and black.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    Tiger head in orange/yellow, black, white and red.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Motto above tiger above an 8 ball.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    University seal.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Shield on blue background. Square.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Black circular, "Princeton University" and tiger in orange.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    AR.2000.064
    Orange and black shield with "1910."
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    Light orange and black shield with "1910."
  - Pith helmet, 1990; 1 box (Box B.17)
    Class of 1970. 20th reunion. With reunion pin.
  - Pith Helmet, 1934; 1 box (Box B.20)
    AR.2000.126
    Class of 1914. 20th reunion.
    Class of 1914
  - Pocket from Class Jacket, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    AR.1995.061
    White and square, "PU" in black, "1905" in gold.
  - Pouch, 1898; 1 box (Box B.10)
    "Princeton '98 Class Day" White leather. Tobacco?
  - Quilted square, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    11" x 11" with tigers and '79.
  - Reunion hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    White, Princeton seal and motto in orange, black and gold, "'73" in black.
    Class of 1873
  - Reunion hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    Orange with black rims, "'79" in black.
  - Reunion hatband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.1)
    Orange with black rims, "79" in black.
  - Reunion patch, Undated; 1 box (Box E.10)
    AR.1997.042
    with bee and 1911.
  - Reunions hat band, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    AR.2001.017
    Orange with black stripes.
  - Reunion visor, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    AR.2003.035
    Class of 1958 reunion visor signed by Jimmy Stewart.
    Class of 1958
  - Sash, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Orange with black braid on edges. "Fiftieth Reunion."
  - Scent bag, 1899; 1 box (Box B.5)
    "79 Ladies Reception June 10, 99" Orange.
  - Shirt, 1969; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Football Centennial with Rutgers "Beat Princeton" - Rutgers T-shirt.
  - Shirt, 1956; 1 box (Box B.7)
    black and orange stripes. Tag on inside "19 Tenth 46"
    AR.1996.055
    John MacFadyen
  - Shorts, 2010; 1 box (Box 38)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. Black shorts.
  - Small cloth, circa 1878; 1 box (Box B.9)
    Black '78 on orange background.
  - Socks, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Orange
  - Socks, Undated; 1 box (Box 15)
  - Straw hat, Undated; 1 box (Box B.15)
    with orange and black band.
  - Sweater, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Black sweater turtleneck with striped sleeves. Orange "P" on front.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Orange.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Orange. "21"
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Orange. "1926"
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Black. "1932"
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Black and orange. Diagonal stripes.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Black and orange. Vertical thin stripes.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Black and orange. Horizontal thick stripes. Knit.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Orange. "98" Knit.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Orange "21" on black background.
    George Packer Berry '21 Collection.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Black with U. seals.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Black with tigers.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Orange with black 27's.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    AR.1998.045
    Black with repeated people, one with "'31" on orange shirt.
    Class of 1931
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Black with orange cannons(?) with "28" on them.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Orange with "753-78" in black. Commemorates 1935 football team's winning season (753 total points vs. opponents' 78).
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Orange, black and white diagonal stripes.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Black with orange "39."
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Lt. Blue. Repeated design of bottles with "VAT 39" on them and half Yale bulldog and half tiger behind them.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 2)
    AR.2003.061
    Class of '98 tie. Orange and black diagonal stripes.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 2)
    AR.2007.029
    Class of 1935 tie. Black tie with orange flags.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 2)
    Class of 1932 tie. Black tie with orange lettering.
  - Tie, 1961; 1 box (Box 2)
    AR.2007.026
    Class of 1916. 45th reunion tie. Black tie with orange stripes and orange lettering.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 2)
    AR.2005.048
    Black tie with orange tiger cartoons.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 2)
    Striped tie and orange and black.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 2)
    Class of 1916 tie. Orange and black stripes.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 34)
    Class of 1942. Black tie with orange logo.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 33)
    Class of 1942. Orange tie
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 37)
    AR.2009.137
    Black tie with orange stripes.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 37)
    Class of 1926. Orange tie with "Princeton 1926" in black and tiger logo.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 37)
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 37)
    Black tie with tiger pattern.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 37)
    Black tie with orange double stripe pattern.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 37)
    AR.2011.041
    Nassoons tie. Black tie with orange stripes and Nassoons logo.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 41)
    Class of 1930? Black tie with orange lettering "30" and tiger face.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 41)
    Class of 1930? Black tie with orange lettering "30" and tiger roaring.
  - Tie, Undated; 1 box (Box 41)
    Princeton Triangle Club. Red tie with gold logo "PTC" with triangle.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Orange. Black bottle in picture, "Vat 49"
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    White with "46" on front.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Gray with '56 "In Vino Veritas" on front.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Orange with 1970 on front.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Orange with '70 and a sailboat on front.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    White with par '70 and tiger on front.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Orange with All-Star Team '70 on back an tigers in front.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    White. 1970 inside cicada with Princeton Shield design. Different Collars.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Blue. Colonial Club.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Black with '57 on front.
    Class of 1957
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    White. Graduate College Shield. Grad-a-pult on back.
  - T-shirt, 1996; 1 box (Box B.16)
    AR.2000.044
    Orange. "Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni Reunions '96". Picture of "The Study of Tiger" Da Vinci.
  - T-shirt, 1998; 1 box (Box B.16)
    White. "APGA reunions '98 Tiger". Picture of "The Study of Tiger" Da Vinci.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Black. "APGA" on front. Tiger and "Graduate Alumni" on back.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Orange. "Princeton Graduate Alumni" and Tiger holding Grad. College on front.
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    White. "Lived Through it. The Renovation of Cleveland Tower. The Graduate College" and before and after pictures of the tower on front.
  - T-shirt, 1997; 1 box (Box B.16)
    White. "Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni Reunions 1997" and picture of "The Study of Tiger" on front.
  - T-shirt, 1995; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Orange. "Graduate Alumni Reunions '95 Princeton" and Picture of a tiger hanging from a double helix.
  - T-shirt, 1999; 1 box (Box B.16)
    White. APGA and tiger on front. '99 and tiger and "Princeton Graduate Alumni" on back.
  - T-shirt, 2003; 1 box (Box 3)
    AR.2007.019
    Take Back the Night Tee Shirt
  - T-shirt, 2003; 1 box (Box 3)
    Ivy Award T-shirt. "2003 Winner of Restaurants and Institutions' Ivy Award."
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
    AR.2005.024
    Class of 1935 T-shirt. White shirt with orange flags "35."
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box 35)
    AR.2009.101
    White Women's Center T-shirt. "This is what a feminist looks like."
  - T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box 35)
    AR.2009.100
    White Chemistry Department T-shirt. Orange and black shield with "Princeton Chemistry."
  - T-shirt, 2009; 1 box (Box 35)
    AR.2009.050
    Black T-shirt. Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni Reunions 2009. "Galileo's Galactic Magic."
  - T-shirt, 2010; 1 box (Box 38)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. Neon green T-shirt and black lettering "Crew."
  - T-shirt, 2010; 1 box (Box 38)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. White t-shirt with "PURR" logo. Princeton University Reunions Run.
  - T-shirt, 2010; 1 box (Box 38)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. Orange T-shirt with black reunions logo.
  - T-shirt, 2005; 1 box (Box 38)
    Class of 1985. 20th reunion. White T-shirt with black lettering "We Won the Clancy!"
  - T-Shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    White. "The Centennial of the Graduate of the Graduate School."
  - White baseball hat, Undated; 1 box (Box B.17)
    AR.2002.043
    Class of 1970 cicada pattern on front and leaping tiger on back
  - White Beer jacket and pants, Undated; 1 box (Box B.13)
    "NBA We did our part."
    given by Frank Buchner '34.
  - White linen knickers, Undated; 1 box (Box B.13)
    Part of reunion costume.
- Series 5: Dishware, 1801-2010; 102 boxes; 12 items
  Dishware includes plates, mugs, beer cans, and bottles, as well as ashtrays, cigarette cases, and class day pipes.
  - 60th reunion commemorative plate, 1984; 1 box (Box A.47)
    AR.2001.030
    Class of 1924.
    Class of 1924
  - Beer can, 1974; 1 box (Box A.8)
    25th for class of 1949, white.
  - Beer can, 1972; 1 box (Box A.8)
    10th for 1962, white.
    Class of 1962
  - Beer can, 1969; 1 box (Box A.9)
    10th for 1959, white.
    Class of 1959
  - Beer can, 1972; 1 box (Box A.8)
    25th for 1947, white.
    Class of 1947
  - Beer can, 1966; 1 box (Box A.8)
    10th for 1956, white.
  - Beer can, 1966; 1 box (Box A.8)
    25th for 1941, orange.
    Class of 1941
  - Beer can, 1964 June 11-14; 1 box (Box 42)
    AR.2009.009
    Class of 1939. 25th reunion. White can.
  - Beer can, 1971; 1 box (Box 42)
    Class of 1961. 10th reunion. Black can with tiger with "61 in 71" logo.
    Class of 1961
  - Beer can, 1980; 1 box (Box 42)
    AR.2009.024
    Class of 1955. 25th reunion. "'55/25th" logo, black lettering on orange background.
    Class of 1955
  - Beer can holder, Undated; 1 box (Box A.42)
    1970 Princeton shield Cicada pattern.
  - Beer glass, Undated; 1 box (Box A.43)
    Orange and Black Princeton seal.
  - Beverage glass, Undated; 1 box (Box A.43)
  - Beverage glass, 1960 June; 1 box (Box A.44)
    AR.2002.047
    Class of 1915. 45th reunion.
  - Beverage glass, 1965 June 9; 1 box (Box A.44)
    Class of 1915. 50th reunion.
  - Black plastic tray, Undated; 1 box (Box A.36)
    AR.1997.020
    with Nassau Hall in silver.
  - Bread plate, Undated; 1 box (Box A.26)
    Orange, with Princeton University seal and motto.
  - Bread plate, 1960; 1 box (Box A.26)
    Color reproduction of McCosh Hall
    EX4933
    Gift of Mrs. Michael S. Lang.
  - Bread plate, Undated; 1 box (Box A.26)
    Small University seal on white plate.
  - Butter dish, Undated; 1 box (Box A.26)
    Small University seal on white dish.
  - Candlesticks, Undated; 1 box (Box A.27)
    Grey with U. seal.
  - Ceramic goblet, Undated; 1 box (Box A.25)
    EX4493
    1' tall, with University seal
  - Ceramic mug, 1899; 1 box (Box A.17)
    Reunions.
  - Ceramic mug, 1914; 1 box (Box A.12)
  - Ceramic mug, 1939; 1 box (Box A.12)
  - Ceramic mug, 1913; 1 box (Box A.12)
  - Ceramic mug, 1914; 1 box (Box A.10)
  - Ceramic mug, 1915; 1 box (Box A.10)
  - Ceramic mug, 1916; 1 box (Box A.11)
  - Ceramic mug, 1915; 1 box (Box A.11)
  - Ceramic mug, 1898; 1 box (Box A.15)
    "1898 Grill Room Princeton"
  - Ceramic mug, 1899; 1 box (Box A.16)
    Reunions. "J.M. Shepherd"
  - Ceramic mug, 1902; 1 box (Box A.16)
    Reunions. "William K. Prentice"
  - Ceramic mug, 1902; 1 box (Box A.16)
    Reunions. "Peter Vredenburgh"
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.16)
    Brown, with university seal and pennants.
    EX5004
  - Ceramic mug, circa 1900; 1 box (Box A.10)
    AR.1995.035
    University seal and 1900 year.
    Class of 1900
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.15)
    Orange wing. "L.S. Jadwin"
    Gift of Emory M. Ford, Jr.
  - Ceramic mug, 1904; 1 box (Box A.18)
    EX4822
    Reunions. "Herbert J. Fraser"
  - Ceramic mug, 1904; 1 box (Box A.18)
    Reunions. "William H. Tower"
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.15)
    Black, 1932.
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.18)
    Black, 1934.
    Class of 1934
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.11)
    Black, barrel shaped, 1906.
  - Ceramic mug, 1957; 1 box (Box A.18)